Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - S
        - Shakur, Tupac (2Pac) - Until the end of time (disc three), 2001; SR-25471; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25470; SR-25469; SR-25472. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # 0-694908401; A-side Matrix # 0694-90843-1 A
        - Shakur, Tupac (2Pac) - Until the end of time (disc four), 2001; SR-25472; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25470; SR-25471; SR-25469. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # 0-694908401; A-side Matrix # 069 490 844-1 A RE-1
        - Shakur, Tupac (2Pac) - Wanted dead or alive, 1997; SR-25473; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Snoop Dogg (Box 428)
          Catalog # INT8P-6115; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6115
        - Makaveli and Shakur, Tupac (2Pac) - The don killuminati (The 7 day theory), 1996; SR-25474; Makaveli; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; E.D.I; Young Noble; Young, Val; Outlawz (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25475. Double Album.
          Catalog # INTLP 90039; A-side Matrix # INTLP 90039 A-1-1-1
        - Makaveli and Shakur, Tupac (2Pac) - The don killuminati (The 7 day theory), 1996; SR-25475; Makaveli; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Wrice, Tyrone (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25474. Double Album.
          Catalog # INTLP 90039; A-side Matrix # INTLP 90039 C-1-1-
        - Shalamar - Circumstantial evidence, 1987; SR-25476; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # V-71155; A-side Matrix # V-1-71155 G-2 B-27489-G2 AL-SP SPO-116548 1-1 MASTERED BY CAPITOL
          Solar
        - Shalamar - Amnesia, 1984; SR-25477; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # ED 5019; A-side Matrix # ST-ED 66930-A-1
        - Shalamar - Wake up, 1990; SR-25478; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # ZAS 2212; A-side Matrix # XSS-2212A-1A G1 (T) A1
        - Shalamar - Over and over, 1983; SR-25479; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # E 9792 (T); A-side Matrix # E9792T-A MT DAMONT
        - Shalamar - There it is, 1981; SR-25480; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # K 13194 (T); A-side Matrix # K 13194 T B-1 -\T/ 7-M TOWNHOUSE
        - Shalamar - The look, 1983; SR-25481; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # 60239-1; A-side Matrix # ST-ES-602391-A F-2 B-18222-AF2 SLM 4631 MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
        - Shalamar - I owe you one, 1979; SR-25482; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # JD-12051; A-side Matrix # YD-12051-A 1S A1 C 1 MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
        - Shalamar - Dancing in the sheets, 1984; SR-25483; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # 44-04949; A-side Matrix # XSS-169558-1A STERLING
        - Shalamar - Over and over, 1983; SR-25484; Shalamar (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25485. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 4936; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-4936-A-2 MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ. L.A., CALIF. 1-1
        - Shalamar - Over and over, 1983; SR-25485; Shalamar (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25484. 2 copies.
        - Shalamar - Full of fire, 1980; SR-25486; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # JD-12153; A-side Matrix # YD-12153-A 1S MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
        - Shalamar - My girl loves me, 1984; SR-25487; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # ED 5034; A-side Matrix # STED-5934A-5 B-20584-A5 SLM 8668 1-2 SPO-1 SH-SP
        - Shalamar - The greatest hits, 1986; SR-25488; Shalamar (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25489
          Catalog # SMR 8615 RM; A-side Matrix # DM B-4812 A-1/4-86 III
          Stylus Music
        - Shalamar - The greatest hits, 1986; SR-25489; Shalamar (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25488
          Catalog # SMR 8615; A-side Matrix # DM B-4811 A-1/4-86 II
        - Shalamar - Take that to the bank, 1978; SR-25490; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # YD-11354; A-side Matrix # YD-11354-A 5S S V MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
        - Shalamar - Wake up, 1990; SR-25491; Shalamar (Box 428)
          Catalog # ZAS 2212; A-side Matrix # XSS-22121A G1 (T) A1
        - Shalamar - A night to remember (Plus remix); On top of the world, 1982; SR-25492; Shalamar (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25493. 2 copies.
          Catalog # K 13162 (T); A-side Matrix # K 13162 T A1-3 7-M F/3 TOWNHOUSE
        - Shalamar - A night to remember (Plus remix); On top of the world, 1982; SR-25493; Shalamar (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25492. 2 copies.
          Catalog # K 13162 (T); A-side Matrix # K 13162 T A1-4 7-M F/3 TOWNHOUSE
        - Sham & The Professor - I am pain; Raise the roof, 2000; SR-25494; Sham & The Professor; Suh Liva (Box 428)
          Catalog # RCR-416-001; A-side Matrix # RCR-416-001-A EUROPADISK DMM NX USA 43354 G
          Red Cent Records
        - Sham & The Professor - I am pain; Raise the roof, 2000; SR-25495; Sham & The Professor; Suh Liva (Box 428)
        - Sham & The Professor - The light's gone out (In my backyard), 1994; SR-25496; Sham & The Professor (Box 428)
          Catalog # PVL 53164; A-side Matrix # MR-50067-A Y3935 0-2 SP S-29900
          Freeze Records
        - Sham & The Professor - Split personalities, 1994; SR-25497; Sham & The Professor (Box 428)
          Catalog # P1 53941; A-side Matrix # MRLP-55024 ARE4 1-1 S-30424 F/W RCE
        - Shamen - Destination eschaton (disc one), 1995; SR-25498; Shamen (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25499. Double Album.
          Catalog # ES 7308; A-side Matrix # XSS7308A-1A
        - Shamen - Destination eschaton (disc two), 1995; SR-25499; Shamen (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-25498. Double Album.
          Catalog # ES 7309; A-side Matrix # XSS7309A-1A
        - Shamus - Big Willie style; Try 2C loot, 1995; SR-25500; Shamus (Box 428)
          Catalog # 174-21294-2; A-side Matrix # 174212941-A Re
          Raw Track Records
        - Shamwell - Do it on the one (Fun in the sun), 1981; SR-30000; Shamwell (Box 428)
          Catalog # MAL 1203; A-side Matrix # MAL-1203-A-DJ-RE-CT2 -L NIX-
          Malaco Records
          Jackson, Mississippi
        - Shanghai Express - Anything goes; The temple of doom (Music inspired by Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom), 1984; SR-30001; Shanghai Express; Lily-Ann (Box 428)
          Catalog # TRS3005; A-side Matrix # TRS 3005 ASB-RE1 MCR
          Team Entertainment Records
        - Shango - Zulu groove, 1983; SR-30002; Shango (Box 428)
          Catalog # CEL 163; A-side Matrix # CEL-163-A A-1 MASTERDISK HW
          Celluloid
        - Shango - U don't have to be a star, 1987; SR-30003; Shango (Box 428)
          Catalog # NS 5501; A-side Matrix # CEL-5501 A AM
          Nova Scratch
        - Shangoya - Shangoya, 1981; SR-30004; Shangoya (Box 428)
          Catalog # SR 1646; A-side Matrix # SR-1646-A PRC-C-1-1-1 MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
          Sapodilla Records
        - Shanice - 21…, 1994; SR-30005; Shanice (Box 428)
          Catalog # 314530302-1; A-side Matrix # 31453-0302-1-A
        - Shanice - Somewhere, 1994; SR-30006; Shanice (Box 428)
          Catalog # 374631163-1; A-side Matrix # 37463 1163-1A 1-1
        - Shanice - I'm cryin'; I love your smile, 1991; SR-30007; Shanice; Hakeem (Box 428)
          Catalog # 3746348171; A-side Matrix # 374634817-1-A SR1 1-1
        - Shankar - Soul searcher, 1990; SR-30008; Shankar (Box 428)
          Catalog # 539 871-1; A-side Matrix # 162-539-871-1-A-SP 1-1 MASTERDISK
        - Shankar, Ravi - The master musicians of India, 1964; SR-30009; Shankar, Ravi; Khan, Ali Akbar (Box 428)
          Catalog # PR 1078; A-side Matrix # PRLP-1078 RVG
          Prestige
          Bergenfield, New Jersey
        - Shanks & Bigfoot - Sweet like chocolate, 1999; SR-30010; Shanks & Bigfoot (Box 428)
          Catalog # Time 163; A-side Matrix # TIME 163-A
          TIME
          Brescia, Italy
        - Shannon - Part time lovers, 1991; SR-30011; Shannon (Box 428)
          Catalog # 848590-1; A-side Matrix # 848 590 1 2 520
        - Shannon - My heart's divided (Re-mix version); Someone waiting home, 1984; SR-30012; Shannon (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-30013. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 748; A-side Matrix # STDM 46481-1 F/W
          Mirage
          Québec, Canada
        - Shannon - My heart's divided (Re-mix version); Someone waiting home, 1984; SR-30013; Shannon (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-30012. 2 copies.
        - Shannon - Give me tonight (The 2000 A.D. mixes), 1999; SR-30014; Shannon (Box 428)
          Catalog # CMC-1013; A-side Matrix # CMC-1013-A PA-1299 MASTERED BY TRUTONE
        - Shannon - Prove me right, 1986; SR-30015; Shannon (Box 428)
          Catalog # DMD 974; A-side Matrix # ST DM 50415-50414-1 1-2 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
        - Shannon - Prove me right, 1986; SR-30016; Shannon (Box 428)
        - Shannon - Urgent, 1985; SR-30017; Shannon (Box 428)
          Catalog # DMD 890; A-side Matrix # ST DM-47534-1 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Shannon - Let the music play; Give me tonight, 1983; SR-30018; Shannon (Box 428)
          Catalog # 49 78589; A-side Matrix # XSS-78589A-1B 2
        - Shannon - Let the music play, 1984; SR-30019; Shannon (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-30020. Different discs.
          Catalog # 821 015-1; A-side Matrix # 160 8210151 A POLYGRAM A 1
        - Shannon - Let the music play, 1984; SR-30020; Shannon (Box 428)
          In same jacket as # SR-30019. Different discs.
          Catalog # 90134-1; A-side Matrix # ST-WTG-835381-B 1-GM 1-1 MASTERED BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Shannon - Let the music play; Dancin' in the key of life (New special remix versions), 1986; SR-30021; Shannon; Arrington, Steve (Box 428)
          Catalog # DMD 950; A-side Matrix # ST DM 49730-1 1-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K.
        - Shannon - Give me tonight, 1984; SR-30022; Shannon (Box 428)
          Catalog # EMDS 6542; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6542 -A RE MB MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
          Emergency Records
        - Roxanne Shanté - Big mama, 1992; SR-30023; Roxanne Shanté (Box 428)
          Catalog # LL 102; A-side Matrix # LL-0-102 A 1-1 CSB
          Livin' Large Records
        - Roxanne Shanté - Brothers ain't shit (Album version), 1990; SR-30024; Roxanne Shanté (Box 429)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4560; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-4560-SR1
          Cold Chillin'
        - Roxanne Shanté - Runaway, 1985; SR-30025; Roxanne Shanté (Box 429)
          Catalog # PA-1410; A-side Matrix # PA-1410-A F/W NS PRESSED AT SOUND MAKERS N.J.
          Pop Art Records
        - Roxanne Shanté - Brothers ain't shit (Album version), 1990; SR-30026; Roxanne Shanté (Box 429)
        - Roxanne Shanté - Round 1, 1985; SR-30027; Roxanne Shanté; Sparky Dee (Box 429)
          Catalog # SPLP 0001; A-side Matrix # SPLP-0001-A SPLP-0001-A MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
          Spin Records
        - Shantelle - Love attack, 1985; SR-30028; Shantelle (Box 429)
          Catalog # PD-011; A-side Matrix # PD-001-A MF HUB
          Pandisc
          Miami, Florida
        - Sharam - Let's get it on, 1999; SR-30029; Sharam (Box 429)
          Catalog # 74321 68991 1; A-side Matrix # B024497-01 B1 KL
          Amtrax
        - Sharaz - Breaker's toolbox volume 1, 1999; SR-30030; Sharaz (Box 429)
          Catalog # 420-007; A-side Matrix # SHARAZ-007-A EUROPA DISK LTD DMM NY USA 37906 C 100-2S-3 2-S
          4:20H! Records
          Sarasota, Florida
        - Sharaz - O-U-8-1-2-Many, 1999; SR-30031; Sharaz (Box 429)
          Catalog # 420-006; A-side Matrix # SHARAZ-006-A EUROPA DISK LTD DMM NY USA 36426 C
        - Sharaz - Serving you, 2001; SR-30032; Sharaz; Wonder Project (Box 429)
          Catalog # 941-019; A-side Matrix # SHARAZ-019-A 53892
          941 Electro
        - Sharaz - The smooth grooves EP, 1998; SR-30033; Sharaz (Box 429)
          Catalog # 420-002; A-side Matrix # 4/2-OH!-002-A EUROPA DISK LTD DMM NY USA 28614 C
        - Sharita - Where is the luv', 1996; SR-30034; Sharita (Box 429)
          Catalog # K4B 022; A-side Matrix # K4B-022-A-THIS EUROPA DISK DMM NY USA 15523 C S-2
          K4B Records
          Norwalk, Connecticut
        - Sharp - Sharp, 1989; SR-30035; Sharp (Box 429)
          Catalog # 60780-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60780-A-3 1-1
        - Sharpside - Fonk ma bitch, 1999; SR-30036; Sharpside (Box 429)
          Catalog # DEL 002; A-side Matrix # 910526-A-
          Records Deluxe
          Belgium
        - Shatasha - Free, 1995; SR-30037; Shatasha (Box 429)
          Catalog # 88561-6325-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-6325-1 A MJS F/W HUBTV
          Ruthless Records
          Woodland Hills, California
        - Shatasha - Free, 1995; SR-30038; Shatasha (Box 429)
        - Shaw, Marlena - Love dancin', 1979; SR-30039; Shaw, Marlena (Box 429)
          Catalog # 43-11025; A-side Matrix # XSS 166207 1B STERLING
        - Shaw, Marlena - Live at Montreux, 2004; SR-30040; Shaw, Marlena (Box 429)
          Catalog # BST-LA 251; A-side Matrix # 3972-BSTLA 251-11(A) S-50178 S-50178
          Blue Note
        - Shawnna - Posted; R.P.M., 2003; SR-30041; Shawnna; Ludacris; Twista (Box 429)
          Catalog # DEFR 15799-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15799-1A X RJ STERLING
          Def Jam South
        - Shawnna - Worth tha weight (disc one), 2004; SR-30042; Shawnna (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30043. Double Album.
          Catalog # B0002950-01; A-side Matrix # B0002950-01-A RJ STERLING 2-1
        - Shawnna - Worth tha weight (disc two), 2004; SR-30043; Shawnna (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30042. Double Album.
          Catalog # B0002950-01; A-side Matrix # B0002950-01-C RJ STERLING 2-1
        - Shawty Coupe - Hit my cell, 1998; SR-30044; Shawty Coupe; Jyn (Box 429)
          Catalog # 9817A2; A-side Matrix # 9817-A-2-A
          Sho-Nuff Records
        - Shayme - Summer night (With u), 1993; SR-30045; Shayme (Box 429)
          Catalog # MRCVIP 1005; A-side Matrix # MRC VIP-1005-A
          Viper 7 Records
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Shea - Poppin' bottles, SR-30046; Shea; Kirkland, Peewee; Cain, Paul (Box 429)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # HIPHOP 911-1010 SHEA A
          Stay Laist Entertainment
        - She - Ms. DJ rap it up!; Rap it up dubwise, 1980; SR-30047; She; Clappers Revue (Box 429)
          Catalog # CL-12-0004; A-side Matrix # CL-12-0004-A
          Clappers Records
        - She - Ms. DJ rap it up!; Rap it up dubwise, 1980; SR-30048; She; Clappers Revue (Box 429)
        - SHE - I want you to want me, 1998; SR-30049; She (Box 429)
          Catalog # INT: 0518486; A-side Matrix # 705-1848-0 A DMM H.P.
        - She - Hello stranger, 1990; SR-30050; She; Waters, Kim (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30051
          Catalog # WAR-075; A-side Matrix # WAR 075 A F/W CSB
          Warlock Records
        - She - Hello stranger, 1990; SR-30051; She; Waters, Kim (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30050
        - She - Hello stranger, 1990; SR-30052; She; Waters, Kim (Box 429)
        - She - Easy money; Handsome stranger, 1981; SR-30053; She (Box 429)
          Catalog # GE-100; A-side Matrix # GE 1000 MB A FW
          Genius Records
        - She Rockers - Give it a rest, 1988; SR-30054; She Rockers (Box 429)
          Catalog # NOTE 14; A-side Matrix # NOTE-14-A HELLO MUM MAX
          Music Of Life
        - Sheeba - I love the music; California dreams, 1988; SR-30055; Sheeba (Box 429)
          Catalog # YRC-786-50; A-side Matrix # YRC-786-50-A MASTERWORK
          York's Records
        - Sheek Louch - One name; Kiss your ass goodbye remix, 2005; SR-30056; Sheek Louch; Carl Thomas; Jadakiss; Fabolous; Sigel, Beanie (Box 429)
          Catalog # KOC-12-5871; A-side Matrix # KOC-12-5871/ A 12-5871
          Koch Records
        - Sheek Louch - OK; I ain't forget, 2003; SR-30057; Sheek Louch (Box 429)
          Catalog # UNIR 21015-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR 21015-1 A
        - Sheila E. - Holly rock, 1985; SR-30058; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2481; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2481-SH2 B-23404-SH2 1-1 12433
        - Sheila E. - Koo koo, 1987; SR-30059; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30060. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-A-2733; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2733A-SH1 16285 CB I-I B-27250 SH1
          Paisley Park
        - Sheila E. - Koo koo, 1987; SR-30060; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30059. 2 copies.
        - Sheila E. - Sheila E., 1987; SR-30061; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          Catalog # 1-25498; A-side Matrix # 1-25498-A-SR2 1-2 CB
        - Sheila E. - A love bizarre, 1985; SR-30062; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30063. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-A-2387; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2387-SH1 B-21983-SH1 SLM 10798 I-I
        - Sheila E. - A love bizarre, 1985; SR-30063; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30062. 2 copies.
        - Sheila E. - Sister fate, 1985; SR-30064; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2335; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2335-SH2 B-21486-SH2 SLM 9999 1-1
        - Sheila E. - Koo koo, 1987; SR-30065; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30066. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20686; A-side Matrix # 0-20686-A-SH1 B-27304-SH1 16329 1-1 CB
        - Sheila E. - Koo koo, 1987; SR-30066; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30065. 2 copies.
        - Sheila E. - Koo koo, 1987; SR-30067; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2733; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2733A-SH1 16285 CB I-I B-27250-SH1
        - Sheila E. - Sister fate, 1985; SR-30068; Sheila E. (Box 429)
        - Sheila E. - The glamorous life, 1984; SR-30069; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30070. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-2145; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2145-SH2 B-19304-SH2 SLM 6646 1-1
        - Sheila E. - The glamorous life, 1984; SR-30070; Sheila E. (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30069. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-2167; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2167-SH2 B-19566-SH2 SLM 7149 1-2
        - Shelley, Pete - Telephone operator, 1983; SR-30071; Shelley, Pete (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30072. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CP 730; A-side Matrix # CP 730 SA HRM A-1 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Shelley, Pete - Telephone operator, 1983; SR-30072; Shelley, Pete (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30071. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CP 730; A-side Matrix # CP 730 SA EMW ESM-1 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Shelley, Pete - Sides of, 1981; SR-30073; Shelley, Pete (Box 429)
          Catalog # SP-133 DM; A-side Matrix # SP-133-SA EMW MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Shello - West coast boogie, 1994; SR-30074; Shello (Box 429)
          Catalog # 0-41450; A-side Matrix # 0 41450-SR1 FUTURE DISC SIDE A
          Giant Records
        - Shello - Another love gone bad, 1994; SR-30075; Shello (Box 429)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7129; A-side Matrix # PRO A-1 7129-SR1 1-1
        - Shells - Why I love you, 2004; SR-30076; Shells (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30077. 2 copies.
          Catalog # J1PV-59960-1; A-side Matrix # J1PV-59960-1SA RJ STERLING
        - Shells - Why I love you, 2004; SR-30077; Shells (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30076. 2 copies.
        - Sheppard, Mel - Can I take you home, 1981; SR-30078; Sheppard, Mel (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30079. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TS 2002; A-side Matrix # TS-2002 A-1A COLUMBIA NY
          The Sound Of Brooklyn (TSOB)
        - Sheppard, Mel - Can I take you home, 1981; SR-30079; Sheppard, Mel (Box 429)
          In same jacket as # SR-30078. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # TS 2002; A-side Matrix # TS-2002 A-1B COLUMBIA NY
        - Sherman, Bim - Miracle, 1996; SR-30080; Sherman, Bim (Box 429)
          Catalog # MNTLP 1004; A-side Matrix # MNTLP 1004 A1 DAMONT
          Mantra Recordings
        - Sherman, Tony - Dancing in the dark, 1983; SR-30081; Sherman, Tony (Box 429)
          Catalog # 601.019; A-side Matrix # 601 019 A1
          Ariola
        - Sherman, Tony - Ellovee-ee, 1983; SR-30082; Sherman, Tony (Box 430)
          Catalog # LS 12 904; A-side Matrix # A 011121293 D-1 PRC-1-1-2-1
          Lakeside Records
          Cleveland, Ohio
        - Sherrick - Tell me what it is, 1987; SR-30083; Sherrick (Box 430)
          Catalog # 0-20883; A-side Matrix # 0-20883-A-SH1 B-30585-SH1 19893 1-1 STERLING
        - Sherrick - Just call, 1987; SR-30084; Sherrick (Box 430)
          Catalog # 0-20674; A-side Matrix # 0-20674-A-SH1 B-28322-SH1 17389 1-1
        - Shider, Garry - Beautiful, 1988; SR-30085; Shider, Garry (Box 430)
          Catalog # MCA-23872; A-side Matrix # MCA 7978 FDS-4
        - Shider, Garry - Beautiful, 1988; SR-30086; Shider, Garry (Box 430)
        - Shimizu, Yasuaki - Subliminal, 1987; SR-30087; Shimizu, Yasuaki (Box 430)
          Catalog # VIH-28295; A-side Matrix # V VIH-28295A 111 F
          Invitation
        - Shimmon/Shimon - Boogie night (Remix); Electric ghost, 1999; SR-30088; Shimmon; Shimon; Sniper & Mystical (Box 430)
          Catalog # SYN010; A-side Matrix # SYN-10-B1
          Vinyl Syndicate Recordings
          Brampton, Ontario, Canada
        - Shimmon & Woolfson - Break of life, 1998; SR-30089; Shimmon & Woolfson (Box 430)
          Catalog # 12 REACT128; A-side Matrix # 12 REACT 128-AA1
          React
        - Shinehead - Family affair, 1990; SR-30090; Shinehead (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30091. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-66629; A-side Matrix # STED-66629-A-1 DMS HERbIE Jr
        - Shinehead - Family affair, 1990; SR-30091; Shinehead (Box 430)
          In same jacket as # SR-30090. 2 copies.
        - Shinehead - Unity, 1988; SR-30092; Shinehead (Box 430)
          Catalog # 60802-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60802-A-1 F/W HERbIE Jr 1-1
        - Shinehead - Gimme no crack, 1988; SR-30093; Shinehead (Box 430)
          Catalog # ED 5362; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5362-A-1 DMS II HERbIE Jr 1-1
        - Shinehead - Chain gang (Rap), 1988; SR-30094; Shinehead (Box 430)
          Catalog # ED 5324; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66741-A-3 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK cg 1-2
        - Shinehead - Sidewalk university, 1992; SR-30095; Shinehead (Box 430)
          Catalog # 61139-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-61139 A-1-DMM SP 1-1 DMS cg
        - Shinomura, Kan - Primitivedge E.P., 2005; SR-30096; Shinomura, Kan (Box 430)
          Signed by artist
          Catalog # FTX-815; A-side Matrix # FTX-815-A XAVIER
          Futago Traxx
        - Shirley & Company - Shame shame shame, 1975; SR-30097; Shirley & Company (Box 430)
          Catalog # VI-128; A-side Matrix # VI-255-GM JR MEDIA SOUND
          Vibration
        - Shiro - Good love, 1998; SR-30098; Shiro; Lord Tariq (Box 430)
          Catalog # 7087 6 13606 1 5; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-13606-1-5 A OASIS DISC MASTERING
          Noo Trybe Records
        - Shock - San Juan; Crack it up, 1983; SR-30099; Shock (Box 430)
          Catalog # D-215; A-side Matrix # P D 215 A
          Fantasy
        - Shock Therapy - My unshakeable belief, 1987; SR-30100; Shock Therapy (Box 430)
          Catalog # SAVE 045; A-side Matrix # SAVE 45 A1 Penthouse
          Fundamental
          York, United Kingdom
        - Shocking Crew - The shocking crew, 1995; SR-30101; Shocking Crew; Celo (Box 430)
          Catalog # CR-338; A-side Matrix # CR-338 A AATB SP
          Shocking Records
        - Shock Taktix - This is not jazz, 1988; SR-30102; Shock Taktix (Box 430)
          Catalog # PT41878; A-side Matrix # PT-41878-AA1 AA1
        - Shocky Shay - No joke, 1989; SR-30103; Shocky Shay (Box 430)
          Catalog # D1-75608; A-side Matrix # D1-1-75608-2 1-DMM SP 1-1 EUROPA DISK DMM